{
    "id": "479011ea70464af0a4061adaac99ee2a",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "....................... you have finished your work, you can go home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "When",
                "While",
                "Until"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t talk ..................... they are singing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "during",
                "while"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "..................... he heard the news, he wrote to me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "As soon as",
                "When",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "They were told to wait .....................… the signal was given.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "till",
                "until",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Put it ………………….. you can find it again.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "where",
                "if"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I will give you a map ..................... you can find the way.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "so that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He thinks that he can buy justice ………………… he is rich.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "because",
                "unless",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You must go ..................... you hear from them or not.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I will forgive you ....................... you do not repeat the offence.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on condition that",
                "in order that",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They fought ....................... bravely that the enemy fled.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}